[{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":36689,"timeElapsed":184630},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679002670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":12316,"timeElapsed":196950},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":15573,"timeElapsed":212528},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":13615,"timeElapsed":226147},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679039610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7738,"timeElapsed":233890},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679045195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5580,"timeElapsed":239475},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":14473,"timeElapsed":253952},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":17099,"timeElapsed":271056},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8996,"timeElapsed":280056},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":51701,"timeElapsed":336413},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679155121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":12981,"timeElapsed":349401},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679174024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":18898,"timeElapsed":368304},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679185201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":11172,"timeElapsed":379481},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679194245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":9040,"timeElapsed":388525},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679201908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7659,"timeElapsed":396188},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679211317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9404,"timeElapsed":405597},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":11675,"timeElapsed":417275},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679238430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":15429,"timeElapsed":432709},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679269661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":25994,"timeElapsed":463941},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8710,"timeElapsed":472656},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8072,"timeElapsed":480734},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679301125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":14668,"timeElapsed":495405},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679306503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5376,"timeElapsed":500783},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679311064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4556,"timeElapsed":505344},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5463,"timeElapsed":510809},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679326024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":9490,"timeElapsed":520303},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679333267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7239,"timeElapsed":527547},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679349424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":13666,"timeElapsed":543704},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":8813,"timeElapsed":552520},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679365988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7742,"timeElapsed":560268},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679373283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":7292,"timeElapsed":567563},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679380164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6877,"timeElapsed":574444},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679387186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":7018,"timeElapsed":581466},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679394423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":7233,"timeElapsed":588703},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679403192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":8765,"timeElapsed":597472},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679411104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":7908,"timeElapsed":605384},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679435317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":22016,"timeElapsed":629597},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679449111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":13790,"timeElapsed":643391},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679461126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":12011,"timeElapsed":655406},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679471338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":10207,"timeElapsed":665618},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679477423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6081,"timeElapsed":671703},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679487930,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10503,"timeElapsed":682210},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679493864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5930,"timeElapsed":688144},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679498975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5107,"timeElapsed":693255},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679506877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7899,"timeElapsed":701157},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679514664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7782,"timeElapsed":708944},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679529896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":12707,"timeElapsed":724176},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679536673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":6773,"timeElapsed":730953},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679545476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8801,"timeElapsed":739756},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679554652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":9172,"timeElapsed":748932},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679563959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9306,"timeElapsed":758239},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679570793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6831,"timeElapsed":765073},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679576627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5830,"timeElapsed":770907},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679585646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":9014,"timeElapsed":779926},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679591006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5356,"timeElapsed":785286},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679622167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":28799,"timeElapsed":816447},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679644696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":22524,"timeElapsed":838976},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679658600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":13900,"timeElapsed":852880},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679664885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6281,"timeElapsed":859165},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679674339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9450,"timeElapsed":868619},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679679531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5188,"timeElapsed":873811},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679685805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6270,"timeElapsed":880085},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679694989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":9179,"timeElapsed":889269},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679699616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4621,"timeElapsed":893896},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679710632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":8915,"timeElapsed":904912},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679715042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4406,"timeElapsed":909322},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679721266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":6219,"timeElapsed":915545},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679728060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":6790,"timeElapsed":922340},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679734214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6150,"timeElapsed":928494},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679744982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":10764,"timeElapsed":939262},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679750527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":5542,"timeElapsed":944807},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679757910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7379,"timeElapsed":952190},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679763797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5883,"timeElapsed":958077},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679776868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":10285,"timeElapsed":971148},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679781215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4341,"timeElapsed":975495},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679787795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":6576,"timeElapsed":982075},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679794023,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6224,"timeElapsed":988303},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679801541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7514,"timeElapsed":995821},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679805974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4429,"timeElapsed":1000254},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679809960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3983,"timeElapsed":1004240},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679817082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7118,"timeElapsed":1011362},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679822541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5453,"timeElapsed":1016821},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679830377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":7832,"timeElapsed":1024657},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679842289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":9931,"timeElapsed":1036569},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679846785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4492,"timeElapsed":1041065},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679851998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5209,"timeElapsed":1046278},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679856112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4109,"timeElapsed":1050392},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679862375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6259,"timeElapsed":1056655},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679866908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4529,"timeElapsed":1061188},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679870518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3607,"timeElapsed":1064798},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679874668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4146,"timeElapsed":1068948},{"subjectID":"3nohv9lywr","prolificID":"67104869a47a61b561900be7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c97117077340e46b5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679881677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":7004,"timeElapsed":1075957}]